Jérémy GAUTRAIS

Front-End Web Developer



PROJECT

After 8 years working in plant protection products registration, I have started a professional retraining in Computer Science. I have learned basics of Web Development by working on personal projects. My objective is to join an IT development team.

CONTACT

+33 (0)6 64 93 27 07

contact@jeremygautrais.fr

★ <u>jeremygautrais.fr</u>

in linkedin.com/in/jgautrais

github.com/jgautrais

Lyon Area, France

Age: 31 | Driving License B

LANGUAGES

French

Native speaker

English

Fluent

German

Intermediate

HOBBIES

Piano
Climbing
Hiking
Vector art, voxel art

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3/SASS

JavaScript, jQuery

React.js

Node.js, Express

MongoDB

Tools

Git, Figma, Adobe Illustrator

Detailed-orientated

Organized

Curious

Project Management

Team work

EXPERIENCE

8 years

Registration Manager

2015 - 2021

Coordination of European projects for development and registration of plant protection products. Biological Assessment Dossiers' writing.

Data Manager

2014 - 2015

Field trials programs set-up and follow-up. Results' communication.

Study Manager

2013 - 2014

Field trial reports' writing, in French and English languages.

EDUCATION

ESITPA – Agricuttural Engineering School

5 years 2013

Uni. Hohenheim - Erasmus (DE)

6 months

High School Diploma, Scientific option

2008